Guide to the Ronald Shiffman collection on the Pratt Center for Community Development 2013.023
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 3: Community Development
  - Sub-series 3.1: Research and Reports
    - Analysis and Assessment of the New York City Alternative Management Program for In Rem Properties, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Analysis of Retail Buying Power and Shopping Patterns in Fort Greene, Brooklyn, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Arts and Community Development -- Bill Strickland, Pittsburgh, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Economic Development, 1997-2003 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Zoning City Planning Commission, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Benjamin Bannekar Academy, 1992-1993 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Bice Wilson / Bruner, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Black/Jewish Conflict, 1975-1987 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Board of Education, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Bommer Macro Study ZIAS 1981 Group (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Bommer Springs Building Community Economic Development, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Bronx Justice Project, 1997-2001 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Brooklyn Application for Federal Urban Empowerment Zone Designation, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Park, 1999-2002 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Brooklyn College, 1980-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Brooklyn Empowerment Zone, 1998-2002 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Brooklyn Empowerment Zone Initative (BEZI), 1997-1998 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Brooklyn Museum Neighborhood Study, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 4-5)
    - Brooklyn Navy Yard Day Care Center Proposal, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Brooklyn Waterfront Proposal, 1994-2003 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Contains one 3 1/2" Floppy Disk
    - Building Strong Communities in New York and Internationally, 1992-1993 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Business Incubator, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Cable Television, 1983-1995 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Carter Brothers Group #1 Business Venture Simulation Presentation, July 23, 1984 (Box 138, Item 297)
    - Carter Brothers Group #3 Business Venture Simulation Presentation, July 23, 1984 (Box 138, Item 305)
    - CDC Support Letters for Empowerment Zone, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Central Area Plan Implementation Commission (CAPIC), 1990-2001 (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Coalition for the Homeless 1986-1989 -- Board Meeting Minutes, 1997-1998 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Community Action Legal Services, 1986-1990 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Community Consulting Services, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Community Consulting Services -- Transportation, 1996-2000 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Community Council of Greater New York, 1986 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Community Development, 1999-2001 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Community Development and Planning, 1979-1995 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Community Development Block Grant, 1981-1982 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Community Development Conference, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Community Development Conference -- New York City Housing Development Corporation; Open City Community Development Conference, 1978 (Box 141, Item 334)
    - Community Development Conference -- Badillis, Smith, Ennis Francis, April 14, 1978 (Box 141, Item 339)
    - Community Development Conference -- New York City Housing Development Corporation, April 14, 1978 (Box 141, Item 332)
    - Community Development Conference -- New York City Housing Development Corporation Discussion and Awards, April 14, 1978 (Box 141, Item 335)
    - Community Development Conference -- New York City Housing Development Corporation Economic Development Workshop, April 17, 1978 (Box 141, Item 338)
    - Community Development Conference -- Summaries of Workshop, April 14, 1978 (Box 141, Item 340)
    - Community Development Conference -- Towards Tomorrow Fair Neighborhood Assistance, 1977-1978 (Box 141, Item 341)
    - Community Development Conference Marrero, 1978 (Box 141, Item 331)
    - Community Development Conference, Open City Conference -- New York City Housing Development Corporation, April 13, 1978 (Box 141, Item 336)
    - Community Development Corporation Funding Conference and Building Hope, 1994-1996 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Community Development Partnership Strategy Annual Conference, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Community Economic Development Challenges and Opportunities of Communities in Transition, undated (Box 142, Item 469)
    - Community Economic Development Council, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Community Economic Development Issues, 1981-1993 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Community Food Resource Center, 1990 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Cooper Square 1989, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Cooper Square Community Development Committee, 1967-1990 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Council of New York Law Associates, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - CPC Manhattan Waterfront Recommendations Matrix, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Crisis of Young Black Men in America -- Geraldo Show, April 18, 1991 (Box 138, Item 300)
    - Crown Heights Area Maintenance Program Champ Strategy, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - CUNY Forum -- Urban Development: Community or Economy, February 27, 2001 (Box 142, Item 437)
    - Day Care, 1988-1990 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Department of Health and Human Services, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Designer/Builder Magazine, 2001 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Development of Self-Sustaining Urban Economies, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Development Plan Bommer, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Downtown Brooklyn BID Impact, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Draft Reports Bommer, 1981-1982 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Economic Development and Manufacturing, 1992-1999 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Economic Development and Manufacturing, 1992-1999 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Economic Development and Merchant Association Surveys, 1979-1981 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Empowerment Strategies, 1993-1997 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Empowerment Zones and Industrial Development, 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 4-5)
    - Empowerment Zones for New York Appleseed 1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Enterprise Zones, 1992 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Essex Street Board of Estimate Meeting, 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Essex Street Management, 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Essex Street Market, 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Essex Street Market, 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 11-13)
    - Essex Street Market, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
    - Essex Street Market Background, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Essex Street Market Contacts, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Essex Street Market Cornell Background, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Essex Street Original, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Essex Street Retail Market Cornell Surveys, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Essex Street Retail Market Physical Layout, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Essex Street RFP Market Analysis, 1983-1986 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Evaluation of the Neighborhood Development Demonstration, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Fiscal Policy Institute, 2000-2002 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Five Year Commercial Development Plan for Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Ford and Rockefeller Community Development Conference, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Ford Foundation Community Development Outreach and Education Campaign Proposal, 1994-1996 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Freeport Mall and Storefront Improvements, 1975-1979 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Grants -- Community Development, 1985-1988 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Gray Rocks Conference on Social Change through Assessment and Organizational Learning, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Greenpoint Historic Designation and Brooklyn Eastern District Terminal, 1982-1998 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Growing South Suburban Action Conference / New Cities, undated (Box 138, Item 314)
    - Hoboken Economic Development and Preservation, 1979 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Housing and Economic Development Testimony, 1982 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Housing Trust Fund and Inclusionary Zoning, 1983-1988 (Box 41, Folder 2-3)
    - Hudson Valley Forum, 1997-1998 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Human Rights Commission News Release on Lefrak City, 1976 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Human Rights Impact Statement New York State, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 6-7)
    - Involvement of Historically Black Colleges and Universities in Economic Development, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Joint Economic Committee, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Legal Services Aiding Community Development Corporations and other PICCED Projects, 1979-1981 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Legislative Women's Caucus, Inc. New York State, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation Community Health, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 9-10)
    - Making it in New York: The Manufacturing Land Use and Zoning Initiative, 2001 (Box 41, Folder 11-12)
    - Manufacturing Communities: Primmer for an Enterprise Zone, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Manufacturing in New York City, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Manufacturing in New York City: A New Mixed Use Paradigm, 1994 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Manufacturing Retention, 1995-2007 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Matchbox Proposals for Community-based Art Projects, 1993-1998 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Media Project Community Media Project to Identify and Share MEdia with Community Groups, 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Mega-Cities, Inc.-- Urban Leadership for the 21st Century New York City, April 24, 1995 (Box 138, Item 306)
      VHS. Runtime: 0:20:00
    - Methodist Hospital, 1967-1973 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Michael Franks -- London, 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Midwest Center for Labor Research (Dan Swinney) Brooklyn Early Warning, 1990-1998 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous -- Human Rights Impact Statement, 1983 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - National Community Reinvestment Coalition (NCRC), 1994-2004 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - National Neighborhood Coalition's Smart Growth Project, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - National Urban League, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - NDP Area of Coney Island, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Neighborhood Economic Development, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Neighborhood Project: An Exercise in Community Planning Workshop, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Neighborhoods: A Self-Help Sampler, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - New Visions Proposal, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - New Visions Proposal Affiliated with PICCED, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - New Visions Proposal Benjamin Bannecker Academy, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - New Visions Proposal Benjamin Bannecker Academy, 1992 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - New York City Partnership, 1996-2000 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - New York City Service Crisis: A Management Response, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - New York Lawyers for Public Interest, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - New York State Legislation, 1980-1984 (Box 43, Folder 22)
    - Northside Williamsburg Clippings, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - Phipps Plaza, 1996 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - PICCED Empowerment Zone Proposal, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - Planners Network Conference, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - Pratt Center Storefront, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - Projection of Needed Businesses in Commerical Center, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Prop Bureau of Economic Analysis, 1996-1997 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - Proposal for A Program of Economic Revitalization for Utica Avenue, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - Proposal for Day Care Service Center, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - Public Markets and Community Revitalization, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - Quality of Life of Mentally Disabled Adults in Community Settings, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - Reinventing Planning in Local Government, 1995 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - Ron Shiffman's Sustainable Development Speech in Lincoln, Nebraska, 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - Ron's Bommer File, 1981-1983 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Shopping Center Projects, 1992-1994 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - Small Retail Business Study, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 11-14)
    - Small Retail Business Study Commission, 1985-1986 (Box 43, Folder 36-39)
    - Small Retail Business Study Commission, 1986 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Small Retail Commercial Rent, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
    - Small Retail Commercial Rent: Small Retail Business Study Commission, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Small Retail Commercial Rent: Small Retail Business Study Commission Executive Summary, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Society for the Preservation of Weeksville and Bedford-Stuyvesant History, 1997-2001 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Special Lincoln Square District, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - SSI Supplemental Security Income, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Steinway Street Survey Forms, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Strategies for Urban Change Ron Shiffman, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Susan Motley/Ron Shiffman Community Economic Development Assessment Study Discussion Paper, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Uprooting Poverty Through Community Development Conference, 1992 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - USAID -- Community Building, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Vocational Education and Benjamin Banneker, 1991-1993 (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Workforce Development, 2006-2007 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Working Capital Fund for Community Economic Development, 1992-2003 (Box 45, Folder 1-3)
    - Young Muralists Workshop and a Parent's Guide to College, 1967-1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Zoning and Retail, 1994-1995 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Empowerment Zones and Enterprise Communities -- Financing Brownfields Redevelopment, 1998 (Box 142, Item 409)
      VHS. Runtime: 1:07:00
    - Enterprise Foundation, March 19, 1985 (Box 138, Item 313)
    - Mississippi Action for Community Education, Birth of a Town, undated (Box 128, Item 173)
      U-matic. Runtime: 1:00:00
    - Mississippi Action for Community Education, We Honor Him Most, undated (Box 128, Item 172)
    - Renaissance in Carroll Gardens? Produced and Directed by Joe Lylé, undated (Box 136, Item 294)
      U-matic. Runtime: 0:30:00
    - Stand with Sisters for Economic Dignity, 2002 (Box 143, Item 388)
      VHS. Runtime: 0:35:00
    - The Microcredit Summit and the Access to Credit Media Project, Faces of Microcredit, undated (Box 143, Item 390)
    - To Make a Break -- Opening of Opportunities Industrialization Center in Philadelphia, undated (Box 130, Item 194)
    - To Make a Break -- Opportunities Industrialization Center, 1964 (Box 130, Item 193)
    - United States Department of Housing and Development -- Now is the Time: Remembering Places Left Behind in the New Economy (President Clinton's New Markets Tour), 1999 (Box 138, Item 362)
      VHS. Runtime: 0:12:15
    - Women's Self-Employment Project (WSEP), 1995 (Box 138, Item 296)
    - Work in Progress on the Community Development Corporation Movement in America -- James Briggs Murray Producer, Director, undated (Box 143, Item 379)
      VHS. Runtime: 0:34:00
    - Workshops and Summaries Reinvestment Conference, May 20, 1976 (Box 141, Item 367)
    - Workshops and Summaries Reinvestment Conference, May 20, 1976 (Box 141, Item 330)
  - Sub-series 3.2: Specific Programs
    - 1314 Prospect Place, Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1984 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Action 1981-1982 Grant #3414-2010/5 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Adopt-A-Building, 1981-1985 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Advocacy Planning at Pratt Eva Neubauer Thesis, 1993 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Asian Americans for Equality, 1983-1993 (Box 45, Folder 10-12)
    - Assessment of the New York City Alternative Management Program for In Rem Properties, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 13-14)
    - Assessment of the New York City Alternative Management Program for In Rem Properties, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
    - Association for Neighborhood and Housing Development, Inc., 1985 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Association of Neighborhood Housing Developers, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Association of Neighborhood Housing Developers, 1983-1984 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Association of Neighborhood Housing Developers -- Weekly Reader, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant News Coverage, 1966-1972 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant 197a Plan, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant 197a Plan, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant 197a Plan, 2004 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant AIDS, 1988-1991 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Data, 1950-1977 (Box 47, Folder 5-7)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Planning for Neighborhood Development, 1977-1978 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Bedford Stuyvesant Rehabilitation Conference, 1966 (Box 138, Item 475)
      .25" Open Reel Audio. Runtime:
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1966-1967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1967-1998 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Annual Report, 1968 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation CBCC, 1976-2015 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Financial Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Financial Statements, 1976-1977 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Fiscal Year Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Fiscal Year Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation News Clippings, 1965-1967 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Photographs -- Robert F. Kennedy, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Research Office Progress Report, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Research Office Progress Report, 1974 (Box 108, Folder 2-4)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Shiffman, Doar Oral Histories, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation's Restore Ball, 1970 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Rose F. Kennedy Center, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Rose Kennedy Foundation Search for Shelter Project, 1988 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Saratogoa Square Urban Renewal, 1992-1999 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Bedford-Stuyvesant Study and Board of Standards Appeal, 1998-1999 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Blitman Construction Corporation, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Brighton Beach, 1991-1992 (Box 49, Folder 1-8)
    - BSRC Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation Newsletter, 1972-1978 (Box 49, Folder 9-10)
    - BSRC Jones 6-14 Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation -- Oral History Transcript, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - BSRC Richardson 21-27 Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1990 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - CDC Community Bd #6, 1993 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - CDCs Miscellaneous File, 1989-2000 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Central Brooklyn Coordinator, 1966-1967 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Community Attitudes in Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1967-1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Community Design Center's Director's Association, 1980-1984 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Community Development Assessment Organizational Development Assessment, 1983-1989 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Community Development Assistance Centers, Sometimes Community Design Assistance Centers (Also Center for Community Change), 1983-1985 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Community Development Conference -- PEN City, Poems, April 13, 1978 (Box 141, Item 333)
    - Community Development Corporation Articles and Papers, 1973-1989 (Box 50, Folder 10-11)
    - Community Development Corporation Materials, 1987-1991 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Community Economic Development Assessment, 1989 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Community Economic Development Profiles, 1972-1974 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Comprehensive and Integrative Planning for Community Development, 1990 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - DARE Reports, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Detroit Collaborative Design Center -- Father Curry, 1994 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Draft about the Pratt Center and Advocacy Planning, 1990-2010 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Economic and Social Conditions in Bedford-Stuyvesant, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Ford Discussion Paper: A Possible Private Sector Initiative for the 1980s, 1979 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Ford Foundation Evaluation of Physical Assets of Mature Community Development Corporations, 1993 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Ford Grant, 1966-1967 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Foundations: New York Conference for Neighborhood Funders, 1984 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Grants Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Housing Trust Fund, 1985-1988 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Initial Evaluation of the Bedford-Stuyvesant Special Impact Program, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - J-51 Legislative Proposal St. Nicholas Neighborhood Preservation Corporation, 1981-1987 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Jennings Hall -- St. Nicholas Neighborhood Preservation Corporation, 1981-1983 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Jennings Hall 85 Bushwick Avenue, Brooklyn -- St. Nicholas Neighborhood Preservation Corporation, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Landmarks Preservation Commission -- Bedford-Stuyvesant Report, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC), 1994-2001 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation (LISC), 1982-1988 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation Program Development Manual, 1991 (Box 109, Folder 1-2)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation and Housing and Urban Development Workshops #1 -- Business Planning vs Program Planning with Neal Nathanson and Charles Rial, undated (Box 143, Item 394)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation and Housing and Urban Development Workshops #2 -- Accounting the Language of Business, Allan Gallant, undated (Box 143, Item 395)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation and Housing and Urban Development Workshops #3 -- Fundraising, Ghebre Selassie Mehreteab, undated (Box 143, Item 396)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation and Housing and Urban Development Workshops #4 -- Highlights, undated (Box 143, Item 397)
    - Louisiana, Katrina, 2005-2006 (Box 52, Folder 7-9)
      Contains one 700 MB CD-R
    - Moderate Rehabilitation Program for Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 10-11)
    - Moderate Rehabilitation Program for Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 12-13)
    - Municipal Art Society of New York, 1995-2001 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Neighborhood Development Support Collaborative, 1989 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - New York State Urban Development Corporation Forum, Pratt Instutute Center for Architecture, April 8, 2005 (Box 142, Item 414)
    - New York State Urban Development Corporation Forum, Pratt Instutute Center for Architecture, April 8, 2005 (Box 142, Item 415)
    - Nos Quedamos Development Organization Tour, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Performance in Black and White: Bedford-Stuyvesant and Development and Services Corporations, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Plan for a Planning and Evaluation Capability Within the Bedford Stuyvesant Resoration Corporation, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Photos: Charles Hobson Community Development Corporations Documentary WRS Animation, 1992 (Box 137, Item 317)
      Betacam. Runtime: 0:20:00
    - Pratt and ACORN Rebuilding in New Orleans, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Pratt Planning Spring Torn off, 1967 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Press Release -- Office of Senator Robert F. Kennedy, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Publications -- Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Re-Assessment of Grants Made to Brooklyn Restoration, Development, and Service Corproations, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Reorganization Plan of Bedford Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation, 1974-1977 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Social Service Outlook Building Rehabilitation, 1966 (Box 53, Folder 8)